SOURITRI MONDAL

souritri1963.mondal@gmail.com

#768, 16th Main, BTM 2nd Stage

Mobile No:9066072795

Bengaluru, Karnataka-560076

• Professional Summary:

Quality-driven Compliance Analyst at Ernst & Young(EY) familiar with tracking, documentation and reporting requirements. Able to assess work, materials and procedures recommend adjustments to maintain compliance. Offering 2 years' experience and a motivated, energetic mindset.

• Work History:

Remediation Analyst

Ernst & Young, Bengaluru, Karnataka

May 2017- September 2018

- The KYC review and analysis done for various customers based on high, moderate and low risks.
- Enhanced Due Diligence research performed for various customers to be individuals, charities, trusts, local public authorities, sole proprietorships, operating entities, company approved and listed on stock exchange through usage of Lexis Nexis and various other tools.
- Inputted data from scanned documents provided by the client in to the computer system and did compliance check for each file.
- Researched and analysed the regulations for each customer type and produced summary report.
- The analysis of various screening results and identification of various hits as OFAC (Office Of Foreign Assets Control) and PEP screening results.
- The review of the disposition reports for the customers having negative news under the USA patriot act and identification of news to be false positive and true hit for the customer.
- The understanding of the various screening results for individuals, operating entities, trusts, local public authorities, sole proprietorships and analysing the details of the disposition based on Adverse News and mitigating the customers accordingly.

October 2018-March 2019

- The review of the various accounts of the clients and identified the legal entity owners for the same.
- The validation of the customer's data on a daily basis and achieved a target of reviewing 300 customer's accounts at the end.
- Assisted and supported Team Leader on preparation of production reports on a daily basis.

• Worked on different line of business and solved more than 50 cases related to different type of customer's to be individual, operating entities, trusts and maintained a quality percent above 90 at the same time.

Quality Control Analyst

April 2019(till present)

- Performing enhanced due diligence check of the customer's data inputted from various documents provided by the client.
- Assisted and helped the team members in review of more cases.
- Supported in the training and mentoring of the team members.

Marketing Intern

Indegene Private Limited, Bengaluru Karnataka

- The preparation of data report of various hospitals from a collective database provided on daily basis.
- The collection of data for Vice President, Senior Vice President and director of various hospitals through usage of social media platforms like LinkedIn.

• Skills:

- Rapid data entry skills.
- Possess good knowledge about compliance, banking and regulations.
- Ability to communicate and share techniques used with other team members.
- Strong interpersonal skills with the ability to establish credibility and maintain good working relationships.
- Ability to maintain good interpersonal relationships within the department and at all levels of the organization.
- Proficiency in MS Excel (VLOOKUP, Match Index Function, Conditional Formatting, Pivot Tables).

• Accomplishments:

• Received Spot Award twice, working as a Remediation Analyst for being the good performer for the particular month and maintaining a quality of above 90 %.

• Certifications:

• Six Sigma Yellow Belt, Udemy 2019.

• Education:

- Master Of Business Administration-Finance and Marketing, 2015-2017 Dayananda Sagar College Of Engineering, Bengaluru, Karnataka VTU- Marks 8.66 (CGPA).
- B.COM Honours: Accounting and Finance,2012-2015 Durgapur Government College, Durgapur, West Bengal Burdwan University- Marks 66%.

• <u>Interests:</u>

- Managing Events.
- Peer Advising.
- Good Communicator.
- Good Dancer.